Cetus-Lupedus! She's back!
Zenon: The Zequel is a family, tv movie, adventure film directed by Manny Coto.
Zenon Kar is 15 and lives on a space station which the
military has taken over and is dismantling.
She receives a mysterious signal and must convince everyone
that it's from aliens who have come to help them.
Zenon Kar, played by Kirsten Storms.
Nebula Wade, played by Shadia Simmons.
Margie Hammond, played by Lauren Maltby.
Astrid Kar, played by Susan Brady.
Mark Kar, played by Robert Curtis Brown.
Proto Zoa, played by Phillip Rhys.
Zenon: The Zequel is a 2001 American science fiction
comedy film directed by Manny Coto.
It is the second installment of the Disney Channel's Zenon television film series, following the first
installment, Zenon: Girl of the 21st Century (1999), and preceding Zenon: Z3 (2004).
The film premiered on Disney Channel on January 12, 2001.
The film is also the first sequel to be produced under
the Disney Channel Original Movie banner.
This is the only Zenon film where Raven-Symoné does not play Nebula.
She is replaced by Shadia Simmons.
The Disney Channel Original Series Lizzie McGuire
premiered after the film's premiere.
This is the last film directed by Manny Coto before his death in 2023.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.